<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WildUtah</string>

    <string name="map_icon_content_description">Map icon to get directions</string>

    <string name="location_photo">Photo of location</string>

    <string name="adams_canyon_description">The trail winds around and eventually meets up
        with a 40ft cascading waterfall at the end.  The trail is steep in some places as
        it gradually climbs up to the waterfall.
    </string>

    <string name="bear_river_migratory_refuge">The Bear River Bird Refuge is 80,000 acres of
        Marsh, Open Water, Uplands, and Mudflats. The refuge is used for birding, fishing,
        hunting, and photography.
    </string>
    <string name="baker_mine">The hike to the mine is brutal. There is no trail and the mountain
        tries really hard to insure that you don’t make it. There is a ton of bushwhacking and
        some rock climbing to get to the top.
    </string>

    <string name="bluebell_mine_description">The trail head is at the base of James Peak. Park
        anywhere on the road and hike to the trail head since it is on private land. This is a
        very beautiful area.
    </string>

    <string name="deuel_creek_description">This hike is fairly moderate in difficulty but it is
        very rewarding.  There are many campsites, pools and even a rope swing to try!
    </string>

    <string name="east_mountain_description">Expect to see many hikers, bikers and even horses.
        The main path is about 1 mile in length and features many different side trails that all
        eventually meet back up to the main trail.
    </string>

    <string name="jardine_juniper_description">The Jardine Juniper Tree is perhaps the most iconic
        symbol of Cache County, and Logan Canyon. The hike is definitely a northern Utah classic.
        The tree is the oldest known Rocky Mountain Juniper.
    </string>

    <string name="bowman_trail_description">The Bowman Trail is a great secret up Millcreek canyon.
        It is moderately and consistently steep, has great views, and can be a half day or full day
        hike.
    </string>

    <string name="double_top_mountain_description">Doubletop Mountain is the second highest peak in
        the Bear River Range, as well as Cache County, Utah. The peak is very close to the Idaho border
        and the trek actually starts in Idaho ending at the Peak in Utah.
    </string>

    <string name="high_creek_lake_description">The entire trail is in the heart of the Mount Naomi
        Wilderness Area. It is one half of the Mount Naomi Peak National Recreation Trail, with the
        other half ending at Tony Grove Lake.
    </string>

    <string name="naturalist_basin_description">For the entirety of the time you will be hiking in
        pine forests with the occasional open meadow affording good views of the close mountain peaks.
        There are many small streams and the area is quite wet.
    </string>

    <string name="notch_lake_description">The trail starts at the Bald Mountain Trailhead and meanders
        around the South side of Bald Mountain. It remains relatively flat and easy.
    </string>

    <string name="white_pine_lake_description">This is quite simply one of the best hikes in northern
        Utah. There are lots of things to see along the way which keeps your brain busy admiring the
        beauty instead of focusing on your lungs.
    </string>

    <string name="alpine_loop_description">The Alpine Loop Drive is one of the prettiest spots in Utah.
        It is also one of the busiest spots in Utah. If you go expecting the crowds its really a gorgeous
        drive. It goes between Alpine and Provo and passes Timpanogos Cave and Sundance Ski Resort along
        the way.
    </string>

    <string name="gandy_warm_springs_description">Gandy is in the middle of nowhere.
        Once you leave the pavement from Highway 6 (Grand Army of the Republic Highway),
        the road is dirt but it is graded and level for most of the time.
    </string>

    <string name="liberty_avon_road_description">The Liberty-Avon Road is a great little
        off road drive that obviously goes between Liberty in Ogden Valley and Avon in
        Cache Valley. This makes a scenic alternative between Ogden and Logan if you have
        extra time.
    </string>

    <string name="little_bear_river_description">Porcupine Reservoir is a beautiful place to go any
        time of year and there is enough to do to make a full day out of it if you want to swim and picnic.
    </string>

    <string name="logan_canyon_description">This Trek is to be used as a travel guide for the
        sights accessible by car in Logan Canyon. The canyon has 10 established campsites some
        of them very large and it has 4 picnic areas.
    </string>

    <string name="tilted_rocks_description">The Tour of the Tilted Rocks is a nice way to spend
        a few hours exploring several things this monument has to offer. There are 15 numbered
        stops with different view points and historical facts.
    </string>

    <string name="colorado_river_description">This short day float, with one rapid, takes you past
        some amazing desert scenery. It\'s short enough to do in an afternoon and still have time 
        to have a BBQ at the takeout, but it's long enough to get any new boaters some experience 
        on a river.
    </string>
    
    <string name="mantua_resevoir_description">
        Mantua Reservoir Trail is a 4.1 mile heavily trafficked loop trail located near Mantua, Utah
        that features a lake and is good for all skill levels. The trail offers a number of activity
        options and is best used from March until November.
    </string>
    
    <string name="mirror_lake_description">Mirror Lake is a 2.8 mile moderately trafficked loop trail
        located near Kamas, Utah and is good for all skill levels. The trail offers a number of activity
        options and is best used from June until September.
    </string>

    <string name="smith_moorehouse_description">Smith and Morehouse Reservoir is a 2.5 mile moderately
        trafficked out and back trail located near Kamas, Utah that features a lake and is good for all
        skill levels. The trail offers a number of activity options and is best used from July until October.
    </string>

    <string name="willard_bay_description">Willard Bay State Park is a 1.2 mile heavily trafficked out and
        back trail located near Willard, Utah that features a lake and is good for all skill levels. The trail
        offers a number of activity options and is accessible year-round.
    </string>

    <string name="arches_description">The park has over 2,000 natural stone arches, in addition to hundreds of
        soaring pinnacles, massive fins and giant balanced rocks. This red-rock wonderland will amaze you with 
        its formations, refresh you with its trails, and inspire you with its sunsets.
    </string>
    
    <string name="bryce_canyon_description">There is no place like Bryce Canyon. Hoodoos (odd-shaped pillars of
        rock left standing from the forces of erosion) can be found on every continent, but here is the largest
        collection of hoodoos in the world! Descriptions fail.
    </string>

    <string name="canyonlands_description">Canyonlands invites you to explore a wilderness of countless canyons
        and fantastically formed buttes carved by the Colorado River and its tributaries.
    </string>

    <string name="capitol_reef_description">Located in south-central Utah in the heart of red rock country, Capitol
        Reef National Park is a hidden treasure filled with cliffs, canyons, domes and bridges in the Waterpocket Fold,
        a geologic monocline (a wrinkle on the earth) extending almost 100 miles.
    </string>

    <string name="dinosaur_description">Dinosaurs once roamed here. Their fantastic remains are still visible embedded
        in the rocks. Today, the mountains, desert and untamed rivers flowing in deep canyons, support an array of life.
        Petroglyphs hint at earlier cultures. Later, homesteaders and outlaws found refuge here.
    </string>

    <string name="golden_spike_description">May 10, 1869 the Union and Central Pacific Railroads joined their rails at
        Promontory Summit, Utah Territory and forged the destiny of a nation. Golden Spike National Historic Site shares
        the stories of the people that define the completion of the first Transcontinental Railroad.
    </string>

    <string name="zion_description">Follow the paths where ancient native people and pioneers walked. Gaze up at massive
        sandstone cliffs of cream, pink, and red that soar into a brilliant blue sky. Experience wilderness in a narrow
        slot canyon. Zion’s unique array of plants and animals will enchant you.
    </string>

    <string name="box_elder_campground">This campground sits near Box Elder Creek and about one mile away from Mantua Reservoir,
        offering plenty of options for fishing, boating and swimming. Hiking, biking and horseback riding along the many trails
        nearby are also popular.The dense Uinta-Wasatch-Cache National Forest offering plenty of shade for most camp sites.
    </string>

    <string name="weber_memorial_campground">Located just west of Causey Reservoir, Weber Memorial Campground has three large
        group areas and nearly 60 individual sites complete with fire pits, picnic tables, flush toilets and drinking water.
        The South Fork of the Ogden River runs through the campground, providing great opportunities for fishing.
    </string>

    <string name="north_fork_campground">This Weber County Park has nearly 200 campsites with access to running water, flush
        toilets and several trails perfect for hiking and biking.Then when the sun sets, make sure to bring your sleeping bag
        out under the night sky for some beautiful star-gazing.
    </string>

    <string name="monte_cristo_campground">This high-elevation campground typically doesn’t open until late June, but once
        it does, it’s very popular with the locals. Located in the Uinta-Wasatch-Cache National Forest, Monte Cristo is the
        highest campground in the Ogden District at 9,000 feet.
    </string>

    <string name="fort_buenaventura_campground">Embrace Ogden’s history, and camp in the first permanent Anglo settlement
        in the Great Basin. Located near the Weber River, Fort Buenaventura was built in 1846, and a replica fort, cabins
        and trading post are still open today.
    </string>

    <string name="willard_bay_campground">This state park is home to three campgrounds — Willow Campground, Cottonwood
        Campground and South Marina Campground — and each have multiple sites with access to restrooms with showers.Each
        campground has easy access to the sandy beaches and water.
    </string>

    <string name="south_fork_campground">The South Fork Campground complex includes several smaller campgrounds: Magpie, Botts,
        South Fork, Perception Park, Upper and Lower Meadows and Willows.Each campground has multiple sites and easy access to
        the South Fork of the Ogden River for kayaking, tubing and fishing.
    </string>

    <string name="bridger_bay_campground">Camp out with the free-ranging bison, mule deer, bighorn sheep, antelope and more
        at this Antelope Island State Park campground. Close to Bridger Bay Beach where there’s access to water, toilets and
        showers, this campground is great for families.
    </string>

    <string name="bountiful_creek_campground">This high-elevation campground doesn\’t open until late June, but when
        it does, you’ll have gorgeous views of the Wasatch Front and plenty of great hiking opportunities.You’ll have to
        access the campground via a steep and winding dirt road, so large vehicles, RVs and trailers aren\’t recommended.
    </string>
    <string name ="campground_1_name">Box Elder Campground</string>
    <string name ="campground_2_name">Weber Memorial Campground</string>
    <string name ="campground_3_name">North Fork Campground</string>
    <string name ="campground_4_name">Monte Cristo Campground</string>
    <string name ="campground_5_name">Fort Buenaventura Campground</string>
    <string name ="campground_6_name">Willard Bay Campground</string>
    <string name ="campground_7_name">South Fork Campground</string>
    <string name ="campground_8_name">Bridger Bay Campground</string>
    <string name ="campground_9_name">Bountiful Creek Campground</string>

    <string name ="campground_1_fee">Fee: $22/night</string>
    <string name ="campground_2_fee">Fee: $20/day</string>
    <string name ="campground_3_fee">Fee: $20/day</string>
    <string name ="campground_4_fee">Fee: $23/day</string>
    <string name ="campground_5_fee">Fee: $20/day</string>
    <string name ="campground_6_fee">Fee: $30/night</string>
    <string name ="campground_7_fee">Fee: $23/night</string>
    <string name ="campground_8_fee">Fee: $15/day</string>
    <string name ="campground_9_fee">Fee: $16/day</string>

    <string name ="campground_1_sites">Sites: 4 group &amp; several singles</string>
    <string name ="campground_2_sites">Sites: 60</string>
    <string name ="campground_3_sites">Sites: 200</string>
    <string name ="campground_4_sites">Sites: 44</string>
    <string name ="campground_5_sites">Sites: several(large &amp; single</string>
    <string name ="campground_6_sites">Sites: multiple</string>
    <string name ="campground_7_sites">Sites: multiple</string>
    <string name ="campground_8_sites">Sites: few</string>
    <string name ="campground_9_sites">Sites: 39</string>

    <string name ="backpack_1_name">Bowman Trail</string>
    <string name ="backpack_2_name">Double Top Mountain</string>
    <string name ="backpack_3_name">High Creek Lake</string>
    <string name ="backpack__4_name">Naturalist Basin</string>
    <string name ="backpack_5_name">Notch Lake</string>
    <string name ="backpack_6_name">White Pine Lake</string>

    <string name ="backpack_1_distance">Distance: 5.7 miles</string>
    <string name ="backpack_2_distance">Distance: 6.44 miles</string>
    <string name ="backpack_3_distance">Distance: 11.54 miles</string>
    <string name ="backpack_4_distance">Distance: 15.5 miles</string>
    <string name ="backpack_5_distance">Distance: 5.4 miles</string>
    <string name ="backpack_6_distance">Distance: 8.05 miles</string>

    <string name ="backpack_1_difficulty">Difficulty: Moderate</string>
    <string name ="backpack_2_difficulty">Difficulty: Easy</string>
    <string name ="backpack_3_difficulty">Difficulty: Moderate</string>
    <string name ="backpack_4_difficulty">Difficulty: Moderate</string>
    <string name ="backpack_5_difficulty">Difficulty: Easy</string>
    <string name ="backpack_6_difficulty">Difficulty: Moderate</string>

    <string name ="backpack_1_address"> 40.696861°, -111.716073°e</string>
    <string name ="backpack_2_address">42.01118N, 111.59671W</string>
    <string name ="backpack_3_address">41.97431N, 111.70912W</string>
    <string name ="backpack_4_address">40.721951°, -110.864152</string>
    <string name ="backpack_5_address">40.688944°,-110.903903</string>
    <string name ="backpack_6_address">41.89493N, 111.64239W</string>

    <string name ="drive_1_name">Alpine Loop</string>
    <string name ="drive_2_name">Gandy Warm Springs</string>
    <string name ="drive_3_name">Liberty-Avon Road</string>
    <string name ="drive_4_name">Little Bear River Salmon Run</string>
    <string name ="drive_5_name">Logan Canyon Scenic Byway</string>
    <string name ="drive_6_name">Tour of Tilted Rocks</string>

    <string name ="drive_1_distance">Distance: 20 miles</string>
    <string name ="drive_2_distance"><![CDATA[Distance: 4 &#189; hour drive]]></string>
    <string name ="drive_3_distance">Distance: 1–2 hour drive</string>
    <string name ="drive_4_distance">Distance: 1–2 hour drive</string>
    <string name ="drive_5_distance">Distance:  39 miles</string>
    <string name ="drive_6_distance">Distance: 10 miles</string>

    <string name ="hike_1_name">Bear River Bird Refuge</string>
    <string name ="hike_2_name">Baker Mine Trail</string>
    <string name ="hike_3_name">Bluebell Mine</string>
    <string name ="hike_4_name">Deuel Creek Trail</string>
    <string name ="hike_5_name">East Mountain Park</string>
    <string name ="hike_6_name">Jardine Juniper Trail</string>

    <string name ="hike_1_distance">Distance: varies</string>
    <string name ="hike_2_distance">Distance: 3 miles</string>
    <string name ="hike_3_distance">Distance: 9.08</string>
    <string name ="hike_4_distance">Distance: About 2 miles</string>
    <string name ="hike_5_distance">Distance: 1 mile</string>
    <string name ="hike_6_distance">Distance: 11 miles</string>

    <string name ="hike_1_difficulty">Difficulty: Easy</string>
    <string name ="hike_2_difficulty">Difficulty: Difficult</string>
    <string name ="hike_3_difficulty">Difficulty: Moderate</string>
    <string name ="hike_4_difficulty">Difficulty: Moderate</string>
    <string name ="hike_5_difficulty">Difficulty: Easy</string>
    <string name ="hike_6_difficulty">Difficulty: Moderate</string>

    <string name ="hike_1_address"> 41.479102°N, -112.267650°W</string>
    <string name ="hike_2_address">Baker Mine, Wellsville, UT 84339</string>
    <string name ="hike_3_address"> 41º 24′ 47″ N, 111º 50′ 36″ W</string>
    <string name ="hike_4_address">40.917337°, -111.863836°″ W</string>
    <string name ="hike_5_address">41° 2’48.02″N – 111°54’17.06″W</string>
    <string name ="hike_6_address">41.81605 N, 111.63267 W</string>

    <string name ="national_park_1_name">Arches National Parke</string>
    <string name ="national_park_2_name">Bryce Canyon National Park</string>
    <string name ="national_park_3_name">Canyon Lands National Park</string>
    <string name ="national_park_4_name">Dinosaur National Park</string>
    <string name ="national_park_5_name">Golden Spike National Monument</string>
    <string name ="national_park_6_name">Zion National Park</string>

    <string name ="paddle_sports_1_name">Colorado River Day Float</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_2_name">Mantua Reservoir</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_3_name">Mirror Lake</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_4_name">Smith &amp; Morehouse Reservoir</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_5_name">Willard Bay</string>


    <string name ="paddle_sports_1_distance">Distance: 9.1 miles</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_2_distance">Distance: TBD</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_3_distance">Distance: 2.8 miles</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_4_distance">Distance: 2.5 miles</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_5_distance">Distance: 1.2 miles</string>


    <string name ="paddle_sports_1_difficulty">Difficulty: Moderate</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_2_difficulty">Difficulty: Easy</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_3_difficulty">Difficulty: Easy</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_4_difficulty">Difficulty: Easy</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_5_difficulty">Difficulty: Easy</string>

    <string name ="paddle_sports_1_address">38.69569, -109.41353</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_2_address">Mantua Reservoir, Mantua, UT 84324</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_3_address">Mirror Lake, Utah 84031</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_4_address">Smith and Morehouse Reservoir, Utah 84036</string>
    <string name ="paddle_sports_5_address">Willard Bay, Utah</string>

</resources>
